Priyanka Vaz

BUSINESS PLANNING MANAGER I





SKILLS

Planning & Forecasting

Demand Consolidation & Prioritization

Analytics

Vendor Management

Project Management

Map Digitization

LANGUAGES

English

Marathi

Hindi

German

ABOUT ME

Individual who has grown in past 12 years from solving complex map digitization issues to now building demand plans for operations planning with an eye for improvisation and experimenting between the how, when, what while constantly refining "so what" for management decision making.

EDUCATION

Masters in Financial Management

N. L. Dalmia Institute of Management Studies and Research, 2016 - 2019

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Mumbai University, 2008 – 2011

Higher Secondary School

St. Andrews College of Science, Commerce & Arts, 2006 - 2008

Secondary School Certificate

St. Francis De Sales School, 2006

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Talent Platform CCO South East Asia

HERE Solutions India Pvt. Ltd. / Mumbai / May 2020 - Oct 2020

Joined CCO South East Asia as part of the 6 months talent platform. It was an experience to be associated closely with revenue marketing, lead development representative, and sales. I gained exposure to how the function works and in turn supported them in improvising their lead generation process.

Assistant School Teacher

St. Joseph School / Mumbai / Jun 2008 - Mar 2010

During my college degree, worked part time to support the growth of kindergarten children. Assisted the main in-charge teacher in developing children through value-based teaching.

City Lead

Camp Diaries / Mumbai / Feb 2019 - Feb 2020

REFERENCES

Linda Francois

HERE Technologies linda.fracois@here.com

Pius Moras

piusmoras@gmail.com

Involved forming a team to run the NGO and recruiting volunteers. Leading a team of 50 volunteers and scheduling extra and co-curricular activities for the development of underprivileged children.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Planning Manager I

HERE Solutions India Pvt. Ltd. / Mumbai / Apr 2022 - Present

Post Re-org after Sep'22:

- Intake demand roadmap plans from Product owners and Content Delivery Managers
- Consolidate demand plans for operations planning and prioritize what to execute when.
- Manage the transition between manual map digitization needs to semi-automation.
- Assess accurate relationship is established between drive/source plan and processing plan.
- Design & execution on annual planning processes in partnership with key crossfunctions, and cross-organization partners (e.g. Long range planning, annual planning, etc.)
- Improve operational excellence through identification and execution of initiatives that create efficiency, remove obstacles, or create improved processes and approaches to the business
- Develop business cases to support and address key strategic initiatives in partnership with stakeholders.

Before Re-org till Sep'22:

- Develop models, reports and analyses towards operational and performance drivers such as headcount, attrition and productivity ~8.5M hours annually.
- Financial performance vs Forecast for €~30M opex

Sr. Business Analyst

HERE Solutions India Pvt. Ltd. / Mumbai / Apr 2019 - Mar 2022

- Developed dynamic models to support multivariate analyses, enable scenario-based excursions, identify drivers, assess sensitivities; maintain model transparency through effective documentation (sources, assumptions, logic, limitations).
- Working with stakeholders across the HERE to support cross-functional projects.
- Creating and communicating forecasted demand reports by individual production site and globally
- Providing relevant data and analytics to support decision making on coding location and timing assignments based upon alignment with Organization strategy.
- Ad-hoc analysis and support for management team.

Business Operations Analyst II

HERE Solutions India Pvt. Ltd. / Mumbai / Apr 2017 - Mar 2019

- Supported operational planning/forecasting.
- Drove analyses to evaluate operations trends and variances at multiple levels (global, functional, site, program, etc.) for deriving inference and supporting in management decisions.
- Collaborated cross-functionally on implementation of planning systems, Integrated Business Planning processes and techniques for operational improvement.
- Distilled complex issues and detailed analysis into simple, structured frameworks and drive key business initiatives and effective changes through concrete operational plans.

Business Operations Analyst I

HERE Solutions India Pvt. Ltd. / Mumbai / Apr 2015 - Mar 2017

- Facilitated monthly, quarterly and annual management meetings and created relevant materials as part of overall operating framework
- Monitored monthly process eficiency improvement at 5 vendor sites
- Managed supplier project readiness
- Conducted weekly meetings with stakeholders for discussions pertaining to projects requiring specific attention.
- Troubleshoot and streamlined future issues that might or will afect projects.
- Monitored changes in planning in various projects & highlighted in various stakeholder reviews.

Spatial Data Analyst II

HERE Solutions India Pvt. Ltd. / Mumbai / Apr 2014 - Mar 2015

- Assessed project-specific training needs of the project team and utilized departmental training materials and/or develop training material according to project requirements, specifications, and project performance targets.
- Created project SOP/Work Instructions and maintained them as per requirement incorporating quality specifications
- Created JIRA project for managing & monitoring issues in the project.
- Monitored & reported weekly project KPI to client and ensured project scorecard is upto date.
- Prepared project management documentation (Project Management Plan and Quality Control Plan).
- Obtained, discussed and follow-through of feedback from client through communication via weekly meetings and emails.
- Assisted with project closure activities.

Spatial Data Analyst I

HERE Solutions India Pvt. Ltd. / Mumbai / May 2011 - Mar 2014

- Quality responsible, subject matter expert.
- Identified, developed and implement advanced Production tools & processes.
- Monitored and delivery project metric to promote data driven analysis for managing deliverables.
- Created or modified HERE digital maps and content databases through the use of proprietary soft wares utilizing digital and analogue source materials.
- Analyzed error trends with assistance in the root cause analysis and corrective action development.
- Organized meetings for project performance reporting and query solving with the team.
- Handled Work Flow Management System and ensuring records are updated correctly for a team of 20 members.